like-ex.com 2014-06-25

# Like-Ex.com - Like Exchange - Free Facebook Likes, Like 4 Like Exchange, Free Likes

**LEGAL PRIVACY POLICY for Like-Ex.com**

This statement was last updated on 10 June, 2013

Like-Ex.com is commited to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your information will be treated as you make use of our web site. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

**Information Collection and Use:**  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us personal information in the form of a valid e-mail address to authenticate users. Contact information from the registration forms are used to get in touch with users when neccessary. Your IP address is automatically logged throughout this site. This information is only available to staff and used for administration and monitoring purposes. Your information will not be sold or used on any other site but Like-Ex.com.

**Cookies:**  
Our site uses cookies to save your login information so you don't need to enter it everytime you come to the site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. However, you must have cookies from Like-Ex.com enabled in order to use most functions on the site. Please note that if we do decide to use third party advertisers they may use cookies. See the appropriate section in this privacy policy for more information.

**Third Party Advertisers:**  
Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users on Like-Ex.com or one of our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Like-Ex.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**External Links:**  
This site contains links to other sites. Like-Ex.com is not responsible for the privacy policies on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read their privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Like-Ex.com. Please be aware that these sites may have age limits and do not state so.

**Public Areas:**  
Please be aware that whenever you voluntary post information to public areas, that information can be accessed by the public and can be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

**Security:**  
User accounts are secured by user-created passwords. We take precautions to insure that account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect user information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to user information to staff who need to access to perform their job functions. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.

**Children s Privacy:**  
Children should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to Like-Ex.com, or anyone online for that matter. This site is not intended for anyone under the age of 18 with the exception of those who are 14 years of age or older and have obtained permission from their parent or legal guardian.

**Correcting, Updating, or Removing Information:**  
Like-Ex.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information based on available options at any time by logging into their account and accessing the appropriate sections in "Account Options".

When your account is deleted for any reason, including you deleting your own account, all or parts of information associated with your account may be retained and not permanently deleted for an undetermined amount of time for history purposes.

**Sharing of Information and Discloser:**  
Like-Ex.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people without your permission except under the following conditions:

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Like-Ex.com s Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

**Contacting Us:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: Admin [at] Like-Ex.com 

_Contact Us_
